export const quizData = [
  {
      "question": "What is the largest living reptile on Earth?",
      "correct_answer": "Saltwater Crocodile",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Python",
          "Komodo Dragon",
          "Leatherback Sea Turtle"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile can change its sex?",
      "correct_answer": "Red-eared Slider Turtle",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Chameleon",
          "Iguana",
          "Snake"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "What is the longest living vertebrate on Earth?",
      "correct_answer": "Tuatara",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Galapagos Tortoise",
          "Crocodile",
          "Whale Shark"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile has the most venomous bite?",
      "correct_answer": "Inland Taipan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "King Cobra",
          "Eastern Brown Snake",
          "Black Mamba"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile can climb vertical surfaces with ease?",
      "correct_answer": "Gecko",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Lizard",
          "Snake",
          "Turtle"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile is known for its ability to regenerate lost limbs?",
      "correct_answer": "Lizard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Snake",
          "Turtle",
          "Crocodile"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile can change its color to blend in with its surroundings?",
      "correct_answer": "Chameleon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Iguana",
          "Gecko",
          "Anolis"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile lays eggs with leathery shells?",
      "correct_answer": "Turtle",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Snake",
          "Lizard",
          "Crocodile"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile is the only one that can fly?",
      "correct_answer": "Draco Lizard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Flying Snake",
          "Flying Dragon",
          "Flying Gecko"
      ]
  },
  {
      "question": "Which reptile has a long, forked tongue that it uses to sense its environment?",
      "correct_answer": "Snake",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Lizard",
          "Turtle",
          "Crocodile"
      ]
  }
]